

Felipe La Yunta

2715 28 St S, Lethbridge, AB, Canada | (+1) 587-257-5588 | layuntaWeb@gmail.com | portifolio-app-nu.vercel.app/

Professional Summary

I am a passionate Web Developer with 3 years of experience in programming. I am seeking an opportunity to be a junior full-stack developer. I am a very practical person, open-minded, and a team player. I am ready to help in any way possible with the technologies I already know and gain experience in those I do not know yet.

Skills

- Frontend: HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Backend: NodeJS, MongoDB, Firebase, SQL, Express, Redux, Python, PHP
- Managing team
- Problem solving

- Speak English, Portuguese, Spanish
- Quick Learner
- Teamwork
- Active Listener

Experience

Full-Stack Developer | Chef's Eye Software

2021 – Present

- ChefsEye is the main project I am working on right now and one of the most complex apps I am building. With a complete backend, complex database relations, and a responsive, simple, and clean frontend.
- Experience with Backend: MongoDB, NodeJS, Express, and Redux.
- Experience building my own API.
- Experience with BCrypt, JsonWebToken APIs, QRCode, Nodemon, Axios.
- GitHub link: https://github.com/layuntaFelipe/chefsEyeSoft

Full-Stack Developer | "Apple" Support Desk

2021 - 2022

- First project where I worked on the front and back end of a project, working on my
 database, and on my own API. Having to learn modern technologies, but in the end,
 every new knowledge learned was worth it, because in the end I had built a real-world
 MERN full stack project that worked perfectly.
- Experience with Backend: MongoDB, NodeJS, Express, and Redux.
- Experience building my own API.
- Experience with BCrypt, JsonWebToken APIs, and Axios.
- GitHub link: https://github.com/layuntaFelipe/support-desk

Full-Stack Developer | House Market App

2021 - 2022

- On this project I worked for myself on building a React app focused on Firebase functionality and design for mobile first.
- Experience with different APIs.

- Experience with Firebase Authentication and Firestore.
- Experience with React Routers.
- GitHub link: https://github.com/layuntaFelipe/house-market-app

Education

Diploma in Computer Information Technology

2021 - Present

Lethbridge College - Canada

Bachelor of Computer Science

2020 - 2021

Technological Federal University of Parana – Brazil

Hobbies

Racing karts

CrossFit

Formula 1

Snowboarding

Reading about business

Traveling